[Section]
Name = Wine Gecko Engine
Version = 2.40
License = GPL
Description = Gecko Engine normally installed on 1st stage setup, but only if internet connection was available at that time. Needed for applications using mshtml.dll.
Category = 14
URLSite = 
URLDownload = https://svn.reactos.org/amine/wine_gecko-2.40-x86.msi
SHA1 = 8a3adedf3707973d1ed4ac3b2e791486abf814bd
SizeBytes = 27959808

[Section.0a]
Name = Motor de renderizado Wine Gecko
Description = El motor de renderizado Gecko se instala normalmente en el primer paso de la instalación, pero solo si la conexión a internet está disponible en el proceso. Necesario para las aplicaciones que hacen uso del "mshtml.dll".

[Section.0404]
Description = 除非當時網路不可用，否則 Gecko Engine 在系統安裝程式的第一階段時已經安装。在使用需要利用 mshtml.dll 的應用程式時需要它。

[Section.0407]
Description = Die Gecko Engine, welche normalerweise während des 1st stage Setups installiert wird, aber nur wenn zu diesem Zeitpunkt Internet verfügbar war. Wird für Anwendungen benötigt, die mshtml.dll einsetzen.

[Section.0415]
Description = Silnik Gecko normalnie jest instalowany przy pierwszym etapie instalacji systemu, ale tylko, jeśli dostępne jest wtedy połączenie z internetem. Wymagane dla aplikacji, które używają mshtml.dll.

[Section.0418]
Description = Motorul Gecko, de redare a conținutului web, este în mod normal instalat împreună cu ReactOS, dacă exista o conexiune Internet disponibilă. Este necesar aplicațiilor care utilizează biblioteca „mshtml.dll”

[Section.0419]
Description = Требуется для приложений, использующих mshtml.dll. Gecko Engine, как правило, установливается на 2-ом этапе установки системы, но только если доступно подключение к интернету.

[Section.041f]
Name = Wine Gecko Motoru
Description = Gecko Motoru normal olarak birinci kurulum aşamasında yalnızca İnternet bağlantısı olduğunda kurulurdu. mshtml.dll'yi kullanan uygulamalar için gereklidir.

[Section.0425]
Description = Gecko Engine on tavaliselt installitud esimeses paigalduse etapis, aga ainult kui interneti ühendus oli sel ajal olemas. Vaja rakendustel, mis toetuvad mshtml.dll peal.

[Section.0804]
Description = Gecko Engine 通常在系统安装第一阶段安装，除非当时网络不可用。使用 mshtml.dll 的应用程序需要它。

