[Section]
Name = Git for Windows
Version = 2.10.0
License = GPLv2
Description = Git is a fast, scalable, distributed revision control system with an unusually rich command set that provides both high-level operations and full access to internals.
Category = 7
URLSite = https://gitforwindows.org/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20170403083756/https://github.com/git-for-windows/git/releases/download/v2.10.0.windows.1/Git-2.10.0-32-bit.exe
SHA1 = 5defdff68265622535b9f0423d9d9b8fb1c90be2
SizeBytes = 32980760

[Section.0a]
Name = Git para Windows
Description = Git es un sistema de control y revision de sistemas rápido, escalable y distribucional con una variedad rica de comandos que proveen operaciones a alto nivel y un control total de los elementos.

[Section.0404]
Description = Git 是快速，可擴展的分散式版本控制軟體，並擁有非常多用於高階操作和對內部的完全存取的命令。

[Section.0419]
Name = Git для Windows
Description = Git - это быстрая, масштабируемая, распределённая система контроля версий с необычно богатым набором команд, который обеспечивает как операции высокого уровня, так и полный доступ к внутренним компонентам.

[Section.041f]
Name = Windows için Git
License = GPL sürüm 2
Description = Git, yüksek seviyeli işlemler ve kendi içine tam erişim sağlayan fevkalade zengin komut setiyle bir hızlı, ölçeklenebilir, dağıtık sürüm kontrol sistemidir.

[Section.0425]
Name = Git Windowsile
Description = Git on kiire, skaleeritav, jaotatud muudatuste kontrollsüsteem ebatavaliselt rikka käsustikuga, mis annab nii kõrge tasemelisi operatsiooni kui ka täieliku ligipääsu siseosadesse.

