[Section]
Name = Neverball
Version = 1.6.0
License = GPLv2
Description = Tilt the floor to roll a ball through an obstacle course before time runs out. Neverball is part puzzle game, part action game, and entirely a test of skill.
Category = 4
URLSite = http://neverball.org/
URLDownload = http://neverball.org/neverball-1.6.0.zip
SHA1 = 51b744f87ee8c435959da1fa0b35472fe02c719b
SizeBytes = 75802818

[Section.0a]
Description = Gira el suelo para mover una bola a través de una pista de obstáculos a contra reloj. Neverball es mitad puzle, mitad juego de acción y toda una prueba de habilidad.

[Section.0404]
Description = 傾斜地板來使小球在規定時間內繞過障礙物。Neverball 是一款半解密半動作遊戲，也是一種對技巧的考驗。

[Section.0407]
Description = Neigen Sie den Boden, um einen Ball durch einen Hindernisparcours zu rollen, bevor die Zeit abläuft. Neverball ist teils ein Puzzle-Spiel, teils ein Action-Spiel und ganz ein Test der Geschicklichkeit.

[Section.0415]
Description = Przechyl podłogę, aby przetoczyć piłkę przez tor przeszkód, zanim skończy się czas. Neverball to gra akcji z elementami logicznymi, która sprawdzi twoje umiejętności.

[Section.0418]
Description = Joc în parte de tip enigmă, în parte de tip acțiune, și un test de aptitudine per total.

[Section.0419]
Description = Компьютерная игра-платформер, в которой игрок управляет мячом путём наклона опорной конструкции в трёхмерном пространстве. Для перехода на следующий уровень нужно открыть цель, собрав для этого определённое количество монет (очков), и попасть в неё мячом.

[Section.041f]
License = GPL sürüm 2
Description = Süre bitmeden önce bir engel gidişi boyunca bir topu yuvarlamak için odayı eğiniz. Neverball, kısmen bulmaca oyunu, kısmen hareketli oyun ve tamamen bir beceri testidir.

[Section.0804]
Description = 倾斜地板来使小球在规定时间内绕过障碍物。Neverball 一款是半解密半动作游戏，也是一种对技巧的考验。

