[Section]
Name = Opera
Version = 12.18
License = Freeware
Description = The popular Opera Browser with many advanced features, including an e-mail and BitTorrent client.
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.opera.com/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20210606230730/http://ftp.opera.com/pub/opera/win/1218/int/Opera_1218_int_Setup.exe
SHA1 = b2344bfd13e85dab4f50c0b579b9a485bf473136
SizeBytes = 12956472
RegName = Opera 12.18.1872

[Section.0a]
Description = Popular navegador web con muchas características avanzadas, incluyendo un cliente de correo y BitTorrent.

[Section.0404]
License = 免費軟體
Description = Opera 是一款流行的瀏覽器。有許多進階功能，包括電子郵件和 BitTorrent 用戶端。

[Section.0405]
Description = Populární prohlížeč Opera s mnoha pokročilými vlastnostmi, včetně vestavené podpory pro e-mail a BitTorrent.

[Section.0407]
Description = Der populäre Opera Browser mit vielen fortschrittlichen Eigenschaften, enthält einen E-Mail und BitTorrent Client.

[Section.040c]
Description = Le populaire navigateur Opera avec beaucoup de fonctionnalités avancées, incluant un client mail et BitTorrent.

[Section.0410]
Description = Il famoso browser Opera con funzionalità avanzate come un client BitTorrent integrato e la gestione delle Mail.

[Section.0413]
Description = De populaire Opera Browser met vele gevorderde mogelijkheden, inclusief e-mail en BitTorrent afnemers.

[Section.0415]
Description = Popularna przeglądarka internetowa z wieloma zaawansowanymi funkcjami, zawierająca klientów: poczty oraz BitTorrent.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Navigator web popular cu multe funcționalități avansate, inclusiv un client de poștă electronică și de BitTorrent.

[Section.0419]
License = Бесплатно
Description = Популярный браузер со многими дополнительными возможностями, включающий клиентов почты и BitTorrent.

[Section.041f]
Description = Bir posta ve BitTorrent istemcisini kapsayan birçok gelişmiş özellikle popüler Opera Tarayıcısı.

[Section.0422]
Description = Популярний браузер з багатьма додатковими можливостями, який включає в себе поштовий та BitTorrent клієнти.

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = 流行的 Opera 浏览器，带有许多高级功能，包含电子邮件和 BitTorrent 客户端。

[Section.0813]
Description = De populaire Opera Browser met vele gevorderde mogelijkheden, inclusief e-mail en BitTorrent afnemers.

