[Section]
Name = Qmmp (Qt-based Multimedia Player)
Version = 0.11.1
License = GPL
Description = An audio-player based on the Qt libraries. The user interface is similar to WinAMP or XMMS. Alternative user interfaces are also available.
Category = 1
URLSite = http://qmmp.ylsoftware.com/
URLDownload = http://qmmp.ylsoftware.com/files/windows/0.11/qmmp-0.11.1-win32.exe
SHA1 = ffe410a53b46a7905a7b80863aba4a37249c5250
SizeBytes = 14754797

[Section.0a]
Name = Qmmp (Reproductor multimedia Qt)
Description = Reproductor multimedia basado en las bibliotecas Qt, la interfaz es parecida a la de WinAMP o XMMS. Existen otras interfaces alternativas.

[Section.0404]
Name = Qmmp
Description = 基於 Qt 庫的音訊播放器。用戶界面與 WinAMP 或 XMMS 類似。亦可以使用其他用戶界面款式。

[Section.0407]
Description = Audio-Player, der mit Hilfe der Qt Bibliothek geschrieben wurde. Die Benutzeroberfläche ist ähnlich zu WinAMP oder XMMS. Alternative Benutzeroberflächen sind ebenfalls verfügbar.

[Section.0410]
Description = Qmmp è un lettore multimediale, scritto con l'aiuto della libreria Qt. L'interfaccia grafica è simile a WinAMP o XMMS. Interfaccie utenti alternative sono disponibili.

[Section.0415]
Description = Gmmp to odtwarzacz audio, napisany z pomocą biblioteki Qt. Interfejs podobny jest do Winampa lub XMMS. Dostępnme są także dodatkowe skórki.

[Section.0418]
Name = Qmmp
Description = Lector audio ce utilizează biblioteca QT. Interfața de utilizare e asemănătoare cu cea din WinAMP sau XMMS. De asemenea, sunt disponibile interfețe de utilizare alternative.

[Section.0419]
Description = Аудиоплеер Qmmp (Qt-based Multimedia Player).

[Section.041f]
Name = Qmmp (Qt Tabanlı Çoklu Ortam Oynatıcısı)
Description = Qt kütüphaneleri tabanlı bir ses oynatıcısı. Kullanıcı arayüzü WinAMP'a ve XMMS'ye benzerdir. Başka kullanıcı arayüzleri de kullanılabilir.

[Section.0804]
Description = 基于 Qt 库的音频播放器。用户界面是类似于 WinAMP 或 XMMS。备选用户界面也是可用的。

