[Section]
Name = Scribus
Version = 1.4.7
License = GPLv2
Description = An open-source program that brings professional page layout to ReactOS.
Category = 3
URLSite = http://www.scribus.net/
URLDownload = https://download.sourceforge.net/project/scribus/scribus/1.4.7/scribus-1.4.7-windows.exe
SHA1 = 644694da09557b30d019f09949c6809db768b2e2
SizeBytes = 84314878

[Section.0a]
Description = Un programa de código abierto que brinda diseño de página profesional a ReactOS.

[Section.0404]
Description = 一款給予 ReactOS 專業的頁面布局的開源程式。

[Section.0405]
Description = Open-source program, který přináší profesionální stránky rozložení ReactOS.

[Section.0407]
Description = Ein Open-Source-Programm, das professionelles Seitenlayout in ReactOS bringt.

[Section.040c]
Description = Un programme open source qui apporte la mise en page professionnelle de ReactOS.

[Section.0410]
Description = Un programma open-source che porta l'impaginazione professionale di ReactOS.

[Section.0413]
Description = Een open-source programma dat professionele pagina-indeling aan ReactOS brengt.

[Section.0414]
Description = En åpen kildekode-program som gir profesjonell sidelayout til ReactOS.

[Section.0415]
Description = Program open source, który przynosi profesjonalny układ strony ReactOS.

[Section.0418]
Description = Program, cu surse deschise, de tehnoredactare computerizată.

[Section.0419]
Description = Приложение для визуальной вёрстки документов с открытым исходным кодом.

[Section.041b]
Description = Open-source program, ktorý prináša profesionálnej stránke rozloženie na ReactOS.

[Section.041f]
License = GPL sürüm 2
Description = ReactOS'a profesyonel sayfa düzenlemesi getiren bir açık kaynak program.

[Section.0422]
Description = Відкритим вихідним кодом програми, що приносить професійний режим перегляду для ReactOS.

[Section.0804]
Description = 一个给 ReactOS 带来专业的页面布局的开源程序。

[Section.0813]
Description = Een open-source programma dat professionele pagina-indeling aan ReactOS brengt.

