[Section]
Name = IndiFTPD
Version = 1.0.9 Beta
License = GPL
Description = A standalone FTP server that functions as a single executable. It is designed for situations when a user does not want to install/configure a server on the system (or does not have permission to do so) and wants to quickly get a server running.
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.dftpd.com/products.php#indiftpd
URLDownload = http://www.dftpd.com/files/IndiFTPD/1.0.9_beta/Windows/Intel/indiftpd.exe
SHA1 = 106b5c86c563ed4d4d1976014a8b2562281e5e2d
SizeBytes = 569344

[Section.0a]
Description = Un servidor FTP autónomo que funciona como un único ejecutable. Útil para situaciones en las que no se quiere/puede instalar un servidor en el sistema y se necesita tener algo rápido que lo supla en un momento.

[Section.0404]
Description = 一款以可執行檔案運作的獨立 FTP 伺服器。它為不想在系統上安裝或設定伺服器（或者沒有權限這樣做）並且想馬上運行一個伺服器的使用者而設計。

[Section.0407]
Description = Eigenständiger FTP Server in einer einzigen Anwendung. Er wurde erstellt für Situationen, in denen ein Anwender keinen Server auf dem System installieren/konfigurieren möchte (oder nicht die Rechte dafür besitzt) und schnell einen Server lauffähig bekommen will.

[Section.0410]
Description = IndiFTPD è un server FTP autonomo che funziona come un unico eseguibile. È stato progettato per le situazioni quando un utente non vuole installare / configurare un server sul sistema (o non ha il permesso di farlo), e vuole ottenere rapidamente un server che esegue.

[Section.0415]
Description = IndiFTPD to samodzielny serwer FTP składający sie z jednego pliku wykonywalnego. Zaprojektowany z myślą o użytkownikach, którzy nie chcą instalować / konfigurować serwera w systemie (lub nie mają uprawnień) i chcą szybko uruchomić serwer FTP.

[Section.0418]
Description = Server FTP de sine stătător, într-un singur executabil. Este adresat situațiilor în care nu este posibilă sau nu se dorește instalarea/configurarea unui server în sistem, însă este necesară obținerea rapidă a unui server funcțional.

[Section.0419]
Description = Отдельный FTP-сервер, который работает как единый исполняемый файл. Он предназначен для ситуаций, когда пользователь не хочет устанавливать/настраивать сервер в системе (или не имеет прав, чтобы это сделать), но хочет быстро поднять сервер.

[Section.041f]
Description = Bir tek çalıştırılabilir dosya olarak tek başına bir FTP sunucusu. Bir kullanıcının, çabucak, çalışan bir sunucuya sahip olmak istediği ve sisteminde bir sunucu kurmak/yapılandırmak istemediği (veya bunu yapmaya izni olmadığı) durumlar için tasarlanmıştır.

[Section.0425]
Version = 1.0.9 Beeta
Description = Iseseisev FTP server, mis funktsioneerib ühe ainsa rakendusena. See on disainitud olukordade jaoks, kus kasutaja ei soovi installida ega konfigureerida serverit süsteemil (või pole õiguseid selle jaoks) ja tahab kiirelt serveri tööle saada.

[Section.0804]
Description = 单可执行文件的独立 FTP 服务器。它被设计成适用于用户不想在系统上安装或配置服务器（或者没有权限这么做）并且想马上运行一个服务器的情况。

