[Section]
Name = Mesa3D Graphics Library
Version = 17.0.1
License = MIT
Description = This build of the Mesa3D Graphics Library consits of Mesa, Gallium and llvmpipe. It provides a significant performance boost for systems with no OpenGL hardware acceleration. It can replace the OGL driver on your system - this can be set during setup or via the OpenGL Configuration control panel applet.
Category = 14
URLSite = https://www.mesa3d.org
URLDownload = http://svn.reactos.org/packages/mesa3d_setup.exe
SHA1 = 4c0d42844ff3693612edfdac51799fd7c63dcafd
SizeBytes = 5978718

[Section.0a]
Name = Librería gráfica Mesa3D
Description = Esta entrega de la librería gráfica Mesa3D contiene Mesa, Gallium y llvmpipe. Te proporciona una mejora significativa en el rendimiento de los sistemas sin necesariamente hacer uso de la aceleración hardware de OpenGL. Puede reemplazar a los OGL drivers de tu sistema - esto puede ser a lo largo de la instalación o a través del panel de control y configuración de OpenGL.

[Section.0404]
Description = 這個 Mesa3D 圖形庫由 Mesa、Gallium 和 llvmpipe 組成。它為沒有 OpenGL 硬體加速的系統提供重大的性能提升。它可以取代您的系統中的 OGL 驅動程式 — 這可以在安裝過程中或通過控制臺的 OpenGL 設定程式中設定。

[Section.0405]
Description = Grafická knihovna obsahujicí moduly Mesa, Gallium a llvmpipe. Poskytuje vyšší výkon na systémech bez hardwarové OpenGL akcelerace. Tato knihovna může nahradit výchozí OGL ovladač na Vašem systému - nastavení lze provést během instalace, nebo pomocí ovládacího panelu Nastavení OpenGL.

[Section.0407]
Description = Beinhaltet Mesa, Gallium und llvmpipe. Signifikanter Geschwindigkeitsschub für Systeme ohne OpenGL Hardwarebeschleunigung.

[Section.0415]
Name = Biblioteka graficzna Mesa3D
Description = Ta kompilacja Mesa3D składa się z Mesa, Gallium i llvmpipe. Zapewnia znaczny wzrost wydajności dla systemów bez akceleracji sprzętowej OpenGL. Może równierz zastąpić aktualnie używany sterownik OGL w twoim systemie - można to ustawić podczas instalacji lub za pomocą apletu Konfiguracja OpenGL w panelu sterowania.

[Section.0418]
Description = Acest pachet este compus din Mesa, Gallium, și LLVMpipe. Oferă un spor semnificativ de performanță pentru sistemele fără accelerare grafică OpenGL. Poate înlocui modulul-pilot din sistem - fie prin instalare sau cu ajutorul interfeței Configurație OpenGL din Panoul de control.

[Section.0419]
Description = Сборка графической библиотеки Mesa3D. Содержит Mesa, Gallium и llvmpipe. Обеспечивает прирост производительности систем без аппаратного ускорения OpenGL. Библиотека может заменить собой системный драйвер OpenGL.

[Section.041f]
Name = Mesa3D Grafik Kitaplığı
Description = Mesa3D'nin bu yapısı Mesa, Gallium ve llvmpipe'tan oluşmaktadır. OpenGL donanım hızlandırması olmayan sistemler için önemli bir performans artışı sağlar. Sisteminizdeki OGL sürücüsünün yerini alabilir, bu kurulum sırasında ya da OpenGL Yapılandırma denetim masası ögesi yoluyla ayarlanabilir.

[Section.0804]
Name = Mesa3D 图形库
Description = 这个 Mesa3D 图形库由 Mesa, Gallium 和 llvmpipe 组成。它为不带有 OpenGL 硬件加速的系统提供重要的性能提升。它可以替代您的系统中的 OGL 驱动 —— 这个可以在安装过程中或通过控制面板的 OpenGL 配置程序中设置。

