[Section]
Name = QB64 (SDL version)
Version = 1.2
License = Freeware
Description = A self-hosting BASIC compiler for Microsoft Windows, Linux and Mac OS X, designed to be compatible with Microsoft QBasic and Microsoft QuickBASIC.
Category = 7
URLSite = https://qb64.com/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20180526110545if_/http://www.qb64.net/release/dirty/2018_05_19__05_07_33-1.2-20180202.85/windows/qb64-1.2-20180202.85-win.zip
SHA1 = 64b8f8d32c24c65598f9d655506fec25c4fb4052
SizeBytes = 102775452

[Section.0a]
Description = Es un compilador auto-compilable de BASIC para Windows, Linux y Mac OS X, diseñado para ser compatible con Microsoft QuickBasic.

[Section.0404]
Name = QB64（SDL 版本）
License = 免費軟體
Description = 適用於 Microsoft Windows、Linux 及 Mac OS X 平臺的 BASIC 編譯器，設計上與 Microsoft QBasic 和 Microsoft QuickBASIC 相容。

[Section.0407]
Description = Self-Hosting BASIC-Compiler für Microsoft Windows, Linux und Mac OS X, entwickelt, um mit Microsoft QBasic und Microsoft QuickBASIC kompatibel zu sein.

[Section.0410]
Description = QB64 è un compilatore auto ospitante di BASIC per Microsoft Windows, Linux e Mac OS X, progettato per essere compatibile con Microsoft QuickBasic.

[Section.0415]
Description = QB64 to kompilator BASIC zdolny do kompilacji własnego kodu źródłowego. Działa w systemach Windows, Linux i Mac OS X. Jest kompatybilny z Microsoft QBasic i QuickBASIC.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Compilator BASIC auto-compilabil pentru Windows, Linux și Mac OS X, conceput pentru a fi compatibil cu Microsoft QBasic și Microsoft QuickBASIC.

[Section.0419]
Name = QB64 (SDL версия)
License = Бесплатно
Description = Компилятор языка BASIC для Microsoft Windows, Linux и Mac OS X. Совместим с Microsoft QBasic и Microsoft QuickBASIC.

[Section.041f]
Name = QB64 (SDL sürümü)
Description = Microsoft Windows, Linux ve Mac OS X için, Microsoft QBasic ve Microsoft QuickBASIC ile uyumlu olacak biçimde tasarlanmış, kendi kendini derleyebilen bir BASIC derleyicisidir.

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = Microsoft Windows, Linux 及 Mac OS X 平台上的自托管 BASIC 编译器，设计上兼容 Microsoft QBasic 和 Microsoft QuickBASIC。

