[Section]
Name = ReMooD
Version = 0.8a
License = GPL
Description = A source port of Doom Legacy. It aims to provide the classic legacy experience with new features and more stability.
Category = 4
URLSite = http://remood.sourceforge.net/
URLDownload = http://download.sourceforge.net/project/remood/ReMooD/0.8a/remoodsetup-win32_08a.exe
SHA1 = 3d91e4feb9f56616a17baeedafc55fd7fe30d560
SizeBytes = 1205484

[Section.0a]
Description = Una versión derivada de Doom Legacy. Su fin es revivir la experiencia clásica con nuevas características y mayor estabilidad.

[Section.0404]
Description = 一款 Doom Legacy 的開源移植。它旨在提供新功能和更好穩定性的經典傳統遊戲體驗。

[Section.0407]
Description = Port des Doom Legacy Sources. Es versucht das klassische Legacy Erfahrung zusammen mit neuen Features und mehr Stabilität zu bieten.

[Section.0410]
Description = ReMooD è un porting sorgente di Doom Legacy. Punta a provedere la classica esperienza ereditaria con nuove funzionalità e maggiore stabilità.

[Section.040c]
Description = ReMood est un portage du source de Doom Legacy. Son but est de fournir l'expérience classique de Legacy avec de nouvelles fonctionnalités et plus de stabilité.

[Section.0413]
Description = ReMood is een broncodeoverdracht van Doom Legacy. Het biedt de klassieke Legacy Ervaring met nieuwe mogelijkheden en betere stabiliteit.

[Section.0415]
Description = Źródłowy port Doom. Jego celem jest zapewnienie rozrywki znanej z klasycznej wersji z nowymi funkcjami i lepszą stabilnością.

[Section.0418]
Description = Portare a codului Doom Legacy, având ca scop de a oferi clasica experiență cu noi funcționalități și o mai bună stabilitate.

[Section.0419]
Description = Очередная версия игры Doom.

[Section.041f]
Description = Doom Legacy'in bir kaynak kodu uyarlamasıdır. Yeni özelliklerle ve daha çok kararlılıkla klasik eski deneyimi sağlamayı amaçlar.

[Section.0422]
Description = ReMooD э Портом вихідних кодів Doom Legacy. Його метою є додати нові можливості та стабільність до досвіду класичного Legacy.

[Section.0804]
Description = 一个 Doom Legacy 的开源移植。它旨在提供带有新功能和更好稳定性的经典传统游戏体验。

[Section.0813]
Description = ReMood is een broncodeoverdracht van Doom Legacy. Het biedt de klassieke Legacy Ervaring met nieuwe mogelijkheden en betere stabiliteit.
